<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Elegant Modern Personalized Photo Wedding Thank You Card &#8211; Bigtarad Reviews</title>
	<atom:link href="https://bigtaradreviews.github.io/show/tag/elegant-modern-personalized-photo-wedding-thank-you-card/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://bigtaradreviews.github.io/show/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 05:01:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.7.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://bigtaradreviews.github.io/show/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/android-chrome-512x512-4-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Elegant Modern Personalized Photo Wedding Thank You Card &#8211; Bigtarad Reviews</title>
	<link>https://bigtaradreviews.github.io/show/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Top 10! Elegant Modern Personalized Photo Wedding Thank You Card</title>
		<link>https://bigtaradreviews.github.io/show/top-10-elegant-modern-personalized-photo-wedding-thank-you-card/</link>
					<comments>https://bigtaradreviews.github.io/show/top-10-elegant-modern-personalized-photo-wedding-thank-you-card/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 05:01:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[weddings]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elegant Modern Personalized Photo Wedding Thank You Card]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://bigtaradreviews.github.io/show/top-10-elegant-modern-personalized-photo-wedding-thank-you-card/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Elegant Modern Personalized Photo Wedding Thank You Card Top 10! Elegant Modern Personalized Photo Wedding Thank You Card &#8211; [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h3>Elegant Modern Personalized Photo Wedding Thank You Card</h3>
<p>Top 10! Elegant Modern Personalized Photo Wedding Thank You Card &#8211; weddings Popular <u>Elegant Modern Personalized Photo Wedding Thank You Card</u>  good product  <i>Elegant Modern Personalized Photo Wedding Thank You Card</i> You can read more about itThis simply chic custom photo wedding thank you card template features an elegant, minimalist, modern design. The default shape is rounded corners, but standard sharp corners also work wonderfully with this design, so try both looks and see which one grabs you! The front features your favorite photo, first names and a &#8216;LOVE and THANKS&#8217; message conveyed with a striking blend of two distinct fonts, with &#8216;and&#8217; in a light, flowing script between the other two words, which are in upper case with a bold, crisp formal look. The &#8216;LOVE and THANKS&#8217; part of the design can&#8217;t be altered. When you edit the front to show your own names, you might change the format to show your first names with last name, or &#8216;Mr. and Mrs&#8230;&#8230;&#8217; or whatever suits your style. On the back, we&#8217;ve set the background as transparent, so that the color of the paper will simply serve as the base color. You can choose a color for the background, if you prefer. The default text color on the back is a slightly softened black, but you can change this if you prefer another color, and you can also change the font and size of the text. We&#8217;ve put some sample text on the back for you to replace with your own message as you see fit, but please don&#8217;t feel restricted by this. If you prefer delete our sample text entirely and keep the back totally blank so that you can write a handwritten note on each card instead, you can do that. Or you might want to replace our text with your own message of gratitude and your own closing and then hand sign your names when you receive the cards. In any case, please do remember to remove all of the sample/placeholder text on both sides as well as our sample photo! We&#8217;ve chosen matte rather than semi-gloss as the default paper choice, as it is well suited to writing your own message on and won&#8217;t smudge. You can of course change this to semi-gloss, or you might consider upgrading to something with a texture such as zazzle&#8217;s &#8216;Laid&#8217; or &#8216;Felt White&#8217;, which can add a feeling of warmth and depth. We hope you&#8217;ll enjoy experimenting with various aspects of this stylish modern wedding thank you card template&#8217;s appearance and make it uniquely yours with the intuitive design tools, your favorite photo and your inspiration! <b>Price:$2.02</b><br /><center> <center></p>
<h1>   <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.youtube.com/redirect?q=https://www.zazzle.com/elegant_modern_personalized_photo_wedding_thank_you_card-256304880482564936?rf=238627982471231924">Top 10! Elegant Modern Personalized Photo Wedding Thank You CardHot PRice: ($2.02)</a> </h1>
<p></center> <a href="https://www.youtube.com/redirect?q=https://www.zazzle.com/elegant_modern_personalized_photo_wedding_thank_you_card-256304880482564936?rf=238627982471231924"><img decoding="async" src="https://rlv.zcache.com/elegant_modern_personalized_photo_wedding_thank_you_card-r_vsh0xe_500.jpg"></a></center></p>
<p> Category : weddings</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://bigtaradreviews.github.io/show/top-10-elegant-modern-personalized-photo-wedding-thank-you-card/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
