<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Simple Modern Baby Photo Thank You Birth Announcement &#8211; Bigtarad Reviews</title>
	<atom:link href="https://bigtaradreviews.github.io/show/tag/simple-modern-baby-photo-thank-you-birth-announcement/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://bigtaradreviews.github.io/show/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 05:04:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.7.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://bigtaradreviews.github.io/show/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/android-chrome-512x512-4-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Simple Modern Baby Photo Thank You Birth Announcement &#8211; Bigtarad Reviews</title>
	<link>https://bigtaradreviews.github.io/show/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Hot Deals! Simple Modern Baby Photo Thank You Birth Announcement</title>
		<link>https://bigtaradreviews.github.io/show/hot-deals-simple-modern-baby-photo-thank-you-birth-announcement/</link>
					<comments>https://bigtaradreviews.github.io/show/hot-deals-simple-modern-baby-photo-thank-you-birth-announcement/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 05:04:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Birth Announcement Cards]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Simple Modern Baby Photo Thank You Birth Announcement]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://bigtaradreviews.github.io/show/hot-deals-simple-modern-baby-photo-thank-you-birth-announcement/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Simple Modern Baby Photo Thank You Birth Announcement Hot Deals! Simple Modern Baby Photo Thank You Birth Announcement &#8211; [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h4>Simple Modern Baby Photo Thank You Birth Announcement</h4>
<p>Hot Deals! Simple Modern Baby Photo Thank You Birth Announcement &#8211; Birth Announcement Cards This item is trending! <i>Simple Modern Baby Photo Thank You Birth Announcement</i>  good product  <i>Simple Modern Baby Photo Thank You Birth Announcement</i> You can order itThis simply charming baby photo birth announcement flat card features a contemporary design that lets you easily customize it to suit your style. We&#8217;ve picked rounded corners as the default shape setting, but you can easily change the look to sharp corners, as that look also works wonderfully with this design. Partially overlapping with the photo toward the top, we&#8217;ve added &#8216;thank you&#8217; in all lower case in a relaxed, modern script that lends a feeling of warmth and familiarity. This &#8216;thank you&#8217; design element and all other text on both sides is in black, except for the elegant gold tone called California Gold that we&#8217;ve chosen to highlight your baby&#8217;s name. You can change the color and font of this name text or any other text except for the &#8216;thank you&#8217; script according to your own taste. If you prefer a more minimalist look, you can delete without replacing any of our sample stats-you might not want to include the time of day or length, for example. Or you might change the format of the date when you edit to show your own detials to show the month before the day, etc. We&#8217;ve set the background on both sides as transparent, to let the color of your paper simply serve as the base tone. You can change this on one or both sides by choosing a color instead, be it a soft blue or pink or anything else. On back, we&#8217;ve added some placeholder text for you to replace with your own message. Though we used all upper case for the placeholder text, you can of course change this look, and you can also change the font, color and size of the text. After you delete our placeholder text, you might decide to simply leave the back entirely blank, so that you can add a handwritten message with your signatures after you receive your cards. In any case, please do remember to remove all of the placeholder text as well as our sample photo! The default paper type, matte, has a soft warmth to it and resists smudging, so it&#8217;s a great choice for writing your own message. Use the intuitive design tools, your favorite photo and your inspiration to personalize this custom photo thank you birth announcement flat card and make it uniquely yours! <b>Price:$2.53</b><br /><center> <center></p>
<h1><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/2714.png" alt="✔" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />  <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.youtube.com/redirect?q=https://www.zazzle.com/simple_modern_baby_photo_thank_you_birth_announcement-256518693622012729?rf=238627982471231924">Hot Deals! Simple Modern Baby Photo Thank You Birth Announcement ($2.53)</a> </h1>
<p></center> <a href="https://www.youtube.com/redirect?q=https://www.zazzle.com/simple_modern_baby_photo_thank_you_birth_announcement-256518693622012729?rf=238627982471231924"><img decoding="async" src="https://rlv.zcache.com/simple_modern_baby_photo_thank_you_birth_announcement-r_vsedcg_500.jpg"></a></center></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://bigtaradreviews.github.io/show/hot-deals-simple-modern-baby-photo-thank-you-birth-announcement/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
